Guide to the Lee S. Shulman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- PROJECTS, Series 5
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - On-site completion interview, entry 2 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Open Entry: Candidate 8 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 8 - entry 1 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 8 - entry 2 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 8 - entry 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 8 - entry 2 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Candidate 8: exercises (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Background Information: Candidate 10 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 10 - student 1 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 10 - student 2 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 10 - student 3 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 10 - student 4 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 10 - student 5 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 10 - On-site completion interview, entry 2 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Assessment of Students #3: Candidate 10 - student 1 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Assessment of Students #3: Candidate 10 - student 2 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Assessment of Students #3: Candidate 10 - student 3 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Assessment of Students #3: Candidate 10 - entry 3 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 10 - entry 1 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 10 - entry 2 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 10 - entry 1 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 10 - entry 2 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Candidate 10: Portfolio Review (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Candidate 10: exercises (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Background information: Candidate 11 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 11 - entry 1 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 11 - entry 2 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 11 - entry 1 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 11 - entry 1 (copy 2) (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 11 - student 1 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 11 - student 2 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 11 - student 3 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 11 - student 4 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 11 - student 5 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Assessment of Students #2: On-site Completion interview - Candidate 11 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Creating a Literary Environment: Candidate 11 - entry 1 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 11 - entry 2 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Candidate 11: exercises (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Candidate 11: exercises, cont. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Candidate 11: Portfolio review (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Background information: Candidate 12 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 12 - entry 1 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 12 - entry 2 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 12 - entry 1 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 12 - student 1 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 12 - student 2 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 12 - student 3 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 12 - student 4 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 12 - student 5 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Assessment of Students #2: Candidate 12 - student 6 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Assessment of Students #2: On-site completion interview - candidate 12 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 12 - entry 1, 2 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Exercixe CX (Computers as an Instructional Tool): Questionnaires (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Exercixe CX (Computers as an Instructional Tool): Candidates B-J (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Exercixe CX (Computers as an Instructional Tool): Candidates K-X (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - DX (Deliberation on a Teaching Problem): Examiner's reports (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Exercixe DX: Candidates A - X (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - LX (Lab Monitoring Situations): Examiner's reports (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Exercise LX: Candidates H - X (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - MX (Alternative Materials): Examiner's reports (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Exercise MX: Candidates B - P (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - SX (Student Evaluations): Pilot Testing Cards, 5/20/1989 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Exercise SX: Candidates A - J (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Exercise SX: Candidates K - V (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - TX (Coping with a Textbook): Examir's reports (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Candidates Notes on TX chapter (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Exercise TX: Candidates B - X (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Spencer Knowledge Growth in a Profession, Reunion, October 1998 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching (S-CEIT), 1989-1994 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching, 1992-1994 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching, 1993-1996 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching, 1st and 2nd drafts, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching, 1st and 2nd drafts, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching, 3rd draft, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education: final report, July 25, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with S-CEIT, 1992-1996 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of S-CEIT, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of S-CEIT, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of S-CEIT, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Notes from February 1993 Interviews with S-CEIT Members (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Responses from Committee, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Drafts of Final Report - S-CEIT, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Outline Drafts, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - S-CEIT Minutes May 12, 1993; S-CEIT Focus Group Report, August 2, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - S-CEIT Agendas, relevant material, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Staff Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Student Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Humanities and Social Sciences Graduate Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Professional Student Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Sciences and Engineering Graduate Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Business School: samples of teaching cases, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Stanford School of Engineering: survey of student opinion of teaching, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Humanities and Sciences Information on Evaluations/Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - School of Education, Stanford Evaluation related materials, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Law School, Evaluation materials, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - S-CEIT 1982-1983, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, Donald: addresses, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Stanford's Teaching Initiative, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Lilly Survey results, Stanford, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Senior Survey 1990 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Departmental Curriculum Review Process (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - WASC Faculty Focus Group (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - WASC Faculty Roles Report (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Department Assessment: American University - Dean's Scholars (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Department Assessment: Central Missouri State University, Art Department Guidelines (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Department Assessment: Cornell University (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Department Assessment: Harvard University (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Department Assessment: Indiana University - Purdue University at Indianapolis (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Department Assessment: Northwestern University (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Department Assessment: Oak Ridge Associated Labs (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Department Assessment: Ohio State University (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Department Assessment: Pennsylvania State University (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Department Assessment: San Jose State University Teacher Scholars Project (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Department Assessment: Sweden Council for the Renewal of Undergraduate Education (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Department Assessment: Syracuse University Teaching Assistants (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Department Assessment: University of Alaska (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Department Assessment: University of Chicago (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Department Assessment: University of Massachusetts, Amherst (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Department Assessment: University of Michigan (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Department Assessment: University of Nebraska-Lincoln (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Department Assessment: University of North Carolina System (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Department Assessment: UT-Austin, College of Natural Sciences (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Department Assessment: University of Washington (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Department Assessment: University of Wisconsin - Madison (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Department Assessment: Virginia Tech (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Department Assessment: Other Interested Universities (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Department Assessment: Notes from Boyer Survey (many universities) (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - "Fostering a Community of Learners: A Reader," 1994 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - FCL (Fostering a Community of Learners) Curriculum Unit Summaries (1996-1997) (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - FCL Course material: Algebraic Functions (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - FCL Course material: Circulatory System (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - FCL Course material: Diary of Anne Frank (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - FCL Course material: Ecology (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - FCL Course material: Election Unit (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - FCL Course material: The Enlightenment (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - FCL Course material: Force and Motion (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - FCL Course material: Frogs: Adaptation (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - FCL Course material: Immigration Unit (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - FCL Course material: Invertebrates (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - FCL Course material: Legal Process in America (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - FCL Course material: Lupita Manana (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - FCL Course material: Of Mice and Men (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - FCL Course material: Persuasion (Mathematics Unit) (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - FCL Course material: Probability (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - FCL Course material: Science Fiction (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - FCL Course material: Scorpions (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - FCL Course material: World Leaders (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Literature Overview: The Giver (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Exit Interviews: Martha, Natalie, Darienne, Doris, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Group Interview, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Learning Theory articles, ca. 1989-1995 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - AAHE Peer Review Project: conference agenda, June 20-25, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - From Idea to Prototype: pilot department teams updates, appendices (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Course Portfolios: Accounting (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Course Portfolios: Business (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Course Portfolios: Chemistry (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Course Portfolios: Computer Science (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Course Portfolios: English (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Course Portfolios: History (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Course Portfolios: History, cont. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Course Portfolios: Mathematics (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Course Portfolios: Mathematics, cont. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Course Portfolios: Music (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Course Portfolios: Nursing (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Course Portfolios: Psychology (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Orin Chein course portfolio, Temple University, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Pat Hutchings course portfolio, University of Wyoming, [1995] (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Frank Langsam course portfolio, University of North Carolina, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Florencia Mallon course portfolio, University of Wisconsin, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Donna Martsolf course portfolio, Kent State University, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Eli Passow course portfolio, Temple University, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Pamela F. Starr course portfolio, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Course portfolio working group: miscellaneous articles (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - "Toward Greater Excellence in Teaching at Stanford," 1995 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - "Acceleration and Reflection in the Role of the Teacher," Lee Shulman, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - AAHE 1989 research forum, Chicago Hilton. Lee serving on the Panel, April 3 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - "Assessing Undergraduate Learning in Sociology," 1992 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - AAHE - Transcript of Shulman Remarks, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - AAHE - Pat Hutchings, December 1993 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - AAHE - Peer Review of Teaching, comments by Shulman, June 1994 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - AAHE, 1990-1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - AAHE - Peer Review of Teaching Conference, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - From Idea to Prototype: proposal draft, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - From Idea to Prototype: proposal, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - From Idea to Prototype: grant support proposal, 1993-1996 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Quinlan/Shulman commentaries, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Participating Departments, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - From Idea to Prototype: project workbook, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - From Idea to Prototype: project workbook (final version), 1995 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - From Idea to Prototype: conference details, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - From Idea to Prototype: conference details, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - From Idea to Prototype: conference details, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - From Idea to Prototype: conference details, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - From Idea to Prototype: registration forms, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - From Idea to Prototype: Project resources (preliminary) (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - From Idea to Prototype: Project resources, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - From Idea to Prototype: agendas, memorandums, etc., 1994 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - From Idea to Prototype: exercises, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - From Idea to Prototype: planning, 1994-1996 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - From Idea to Prototype: planning, 1994-1997 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - From Idea to Prototype: planning, 1994-1997 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - From Idea to Prototype: All-project meeting, June 1997 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - PEER Review and Assesment: Lilly Proposal (original) 1990 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - PEER Review and Assesment: Lilly Report (final project report, 1994) (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - PEER Review and Assesment: PEW Charitable Trusts: First two years - final report (June 1996) (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - PEER Review and Assesment: The first two years (1995-1996) (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - PEER Review and Assesment: PEER Review project workshop materials (1996) (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - PEER Review and Assesment: PEER review workshop modules (1996) (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Course Portfolio Project: correspondence and publications, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Course Portfolio Project: Shulman/Hutchings correspondence, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Course Portfolio Project: Workshops, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Pedagogical Colloquium (1990-1995): miscellaneous papers, surveys, correspondence (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Pedagogical Colloquium (1997): Pat Hutchings, "The Pedagogical Colloquim: Taking Teaching Seriously in the Faculty Hiring Process" (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Pedagogical Colloquium (1997): miscellanous articles: Shulman, Hutchings, Gonnerman, etc. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Pedagogical Colloquim (1996-1997): Draft publication materials on PC model, including booklets (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Pedagogical Colloquim (1997): follow-up to 2/97 Pedagogical Colloquim meeting (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Pedagogical Colloquim (1996-1997): materials on Pedagogical Colloquim from 2/97 meeting, participants (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Pedagogical Colloquim (1997): 2/97 pre-meeting materials (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Pedagogical Colloquim (1997): 2/97 meeting handouts (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Pedagogical Colloquim (1997): transcript and 2/97 Pedagogical Colloquim meeting materials (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Pedagogical Colloquim (1998): 2/98 Kent State meeting, miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - AAHE Peer Review: Project Records (Box 67, Folder 15)
- MISCELLANEOUS, Series 6
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1971, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Shulman: Datebooks, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Notes and News: Michigan State University education newsletter, March 1978-July 6, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Notes and News: Michigan State University education newsletter, July 1976-February 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Technical Proposal for an Institute for Research on Teaching," volume 1, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Written Simulations for Medical Education, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American College of Emergency Physicians (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Papers on Ethnography, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - VTS material, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Decision making publications (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cognitive Styles (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lyman Briggs Convocation (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous articles, education (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Articles translated from Chinese (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NIE Delegation to China (Vitas, etc.), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pupil Mediation: exemplars for paradigm chapter, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Schenley High School Teacher Center, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Schenley High School Teacher Center, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Schenley High School Teacher Center, 1986: content areas (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Knowledge Growth in a Profession: assorted papers and articles (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Domains of Inquiry in Teacher Education: Doyle Chapter for Handbook of Research, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Teacher Program Area (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Core Curriculum Committee, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Core Curriculum Committee, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - U.C. System - Teacher Education (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Second UCSMP International Conference on Mathematics Education, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Shulman Library, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Second National Conference on Assessment in Higher Education, June 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Minorities Conference, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Teaching Handbooks (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Teacher's Workplace Conference, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous notes, documents, etc. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on Teaching as a Profession, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - General Budget (Stanford University School of Education), 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - AERA overheads (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Robert Merton: Self-fulfilling prophecy: history, notes, correspondence, ca. 1975-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Robert Merton: Self-fulfilling prophecy: history, notes, correspondence, ca. 1975-1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Robert Merton: Self-fulfilling prophecy: history, notes, correspondence, ca. 1975-1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Robert Merton: Self-fulfilling prophecy: history, notes, correspondence, ca. 1975-1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - AERA - Spoof Speech, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "Delicatessens," [ca. 1973?] (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - National Conference on Studies in Teaching, "Teaching as Elinical Information Processing," Lee Shulman as participant, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Press Release on IRT [Institute for Research on Teaching], 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Distinguished Faculty Award, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Biographical Sketch/Vita - Shulman, ca. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Comments on Reports from outside Reviewers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Forum '87: Media Coverage (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "Opening Lines: Approaches to the Scholarship of Teaching and Learning," 2000 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - "Lee Shulman" in Fifty Modern Thinkers on Education: From Piaget to the Present, December 2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Shulman: miscellaneous memo's, publications, etc.: 1987-2003 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Shulman miscellaneous, 1997-2006 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Award: "Walking in Your Footsteps - Thank You Lee! The Members of the CPED, 2007-2010." Signed pair of tennis shoes. (Box 8)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH.2014-039; 0.5 Linear feet
  - Education 269 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Strober, Myra (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Wilson & Wineburg, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, S.M., & Wineburg, S.S., "Peering at History" (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Westheimer, Joel (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Walker, Keepes, Chang, "Computers in CA High Schools.", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Walker, Decker, 1977-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Understanding Pedagogy: Research for Improvement of Teaching. Shulman. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sykes, Judge, Devaney, "The Needs of Children and..." (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gary Sykes (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Brief Report on TAP Mock Board Meeting, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lee Shulman, 2006 April 24; 1.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lee Shulman Audio - Symposium on Civic Engagement and Graduate Education, 2006 Apr 24; 1.2; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1)
  - American Educational Research Association: Invited Presidential Session. Grawemeyer Award in Education. James P. Comer 2007 Recipient, Lee S. Shulman 2006 Recipient, 2007 Apr 10; 1.3; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1)